We're going to be beginning the italic capital letters.
Now the italic capitals are based on a particular proportion scale, and I'd like to show you that.
That's the letters are all eight pen widths tall.
I'm going to be working with a pen.
I'm using a C1 size, which is an eighth of an inch.
You can use either a dip pen, as I'm using, or you can use a marker pen.
But the letters should be measured, and you should give yourself guidelines where I've made a stack of eight pen widths, and that's going to be the height of my letters.
So if I make an italic B, it's going to fit into this space, just like that.
Hopefully with a little more ink in the pen.
So we're going to be starting there.
So you'll need to have some paper.
I use gridded paper.
You're going to need a straight edge, or a ruler, a pencil and some sort of writing instrument.